kcsoftwares.com 2013-09-22

# PRIVACY POLICYThe Privacy Policy will address the following points:What information, if any, is collected as a result of your visit? Whether information is shared?Whether Cookies are placed on your hard drive?Contact InformationIntroduction

                                                  PRIVACY POLICY
The Privacy Policy will address the following points:
What information, if any, is collected as a result of your visit?
Whether information is shared?
Whether Cookies are placed on your hard drive?
Contact Information
Introduction
Protecting personal information is a core KC Softwares value. This privacy statement describes how we collect and
use the personal information you provide on our website. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the
use of your personal information and the steps you can take to access this information and to request that we correct
or delete it.
KC Softwares abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the
collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Information Collection
Most websites gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol
(IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp,
and click-stream data. They may use this information, which does not identify individual visitors, to analyze trends,
to administer the website, to track visitors’ movements around the site and to gather information about the
geographic location of our visitors as a whole. We do not collect any such information from our visitors.
Additionally, we do not collect Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) about our visitors at this website. No
information regarding our visitors is collected at this website in any manner whatsoever or for any purpose.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website.
When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user
preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is
being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.
We do not use cookies, and therefore do not automatically record information when you visit our website.
Sharing of Information
As described above, no information is captured by visiting our website. Therefore, no information may be shared
with any third party.
Policy Changes
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will
post those changes in a conspicuous manner to this Privacy Policy, and other places we deem appropriate, so that
you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
KC Softwares
E-mail: contact@kcsoftwares.com
                                                    © KC Softwares
All trademarks are the property of their respective owners. All Rights Reserved.
